

M. Majd Makkieh

Web Developer

Contact Details

Mobil

0176-60441973

Email:

clvansa@gmail.com

Addresse:

Orankestraße 49a, 13053 Berlin

Github:

<u>clvansa</u>

LinkedIn:

majd-makkieh

Website:

portfolio.clvansa.de

Skills

Programming languages

JavaScript HTML / CSS

Sass

Node.js

jQuery

Pvthon

Frameworks / Databases

MFRN

React Native

Npm

Bootstrap

Mongodb

Firebase

PC skills / Systems

Adobe Photoshop

Linus

Microsoft Office (Word, Excel)

Visual Studio Windows

Languages

Arabisch: Native language Deutsch: Level B1/B2 Englisch: Level A2/B1

Personal Profile

Full-stack web developer with more than 7 years of experience in accounting.

I am currently looking for a full time job in web development and ready for new challenges. A high level of professionalism and flexibility are important to me. I have the ability to develop programming systems and languages on an autodidactic basis.

Work Experience

Accountant at the Mayoshop Food Appetizers in Damascus, Syria JAN 2009 - DEC 2014

- Execution of all bookings for accounts of customers, suppliers, banks
- Fund transactions
- Management of inventory system accounts
- Determination of the profitability of individual production units
- Annual accounts, final accounts, budgets
- Management of the salaries of all employees

Accountant at Sadar Cosmetic in Damascus, Syria

MAR 2007 - SEPT 2008

Examination, procurement, inventory, control of cash accounts (accounting databases)

Calculation of the operating and production costs

Final audit of production costs

Education

DCI Digital Career Institute gGmbH in Berlin

NOV 2019 - DEC 2020

Further training to become a full-stack web developer

- one year full-time education
- including technologies of the MERN stack
- several small and a final large practical project

DCI Digital Career Institute gGmbH in Berlin

SEPT 2019 - OCT 2019

Qualification "test center for digital professions" for training as a web developer

Udacity (Online-course)

MAY 2018 - AUG 2018

Further training to become a programmer

- Full Stack Developer Track

Integration and language courses in Germany

DEC 2015 - AUG 2019

Job-related German language promotion B2 at the Europa Spracheninstitut in Berlin.

Integration course at FAW gGmbH in Fürstenwalde.

German introductory course (300 h) in Heinersdorf

Degree in Economics and Commerce in Damascus, Syria SEPT 2005 - AUG 2008

- Technical college for accounting and finance
- Focus on "accounting" with the predicate "good"

High school commerce and trade in Damascus, Syria

SEPT 2002 - AUG 2005

Acquisition of the general university entrance qualification